steelmint.com 2019-12-10

# Steel Coal and Metal Scrap Tenders News, Price and Research Reports SteelMint

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY ACCESSING OR USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTAND, AND AGREE TO BE BOUND TO ALL THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS, EXIT THIS PAGE AND DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE.

At SteelMint Info Services LLP, privacy issues are of high priority. We regard and are resolved to ensure your protection. By using our website <https://www.steelmint.com>, you are accepting the practices described in the Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on our website. Subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices.

Should we ask you to provide any information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions during registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, then you may please write to us at info@steelmint.com.

  1. **Personal Information**

To avail the Services of our Website, you understand and agree that you may be asked to provide Personal Information as part of the registration process and at other points in using the services, and that we will store information that you provide. At various points and/or stages in using and/or availing the Services you may also need to provide additional Personal Information so that we can perform tasks you request in the Services. Subject to the requirements of applicable law, we shall not at any time without your permission, disclose any specific Personal Information which is gathered by us as per this Policy, to any third parties.

  2. **Information Collection And Use**

We use third party payment gateway services to collect payment from you, if you opt for online payment on our website/mobile app. We don’t have any control over the card detail collection part and we don’t store any of your details pertaining to payment mode/card you have opted for in our database.We don’t get any card details, in return, from the payment gateway after successful/failed transactions on our website/mobile app. We are not liable for any type of misusages, if any,that happens on your card after making payment on our website/mobile app.

  3. **Links to other websites**

At times, we may link to other sites. Once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over the other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information, which you provide whilst visiting such sites and this privacy statement does not govern such sites. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

  4. **Cookies**

To facilitate and customize your experience with the website, we may store cookies on your computer. Cookies are files that your web browser puts on your computer when you visit a website. We may use cookies to record how often you visit our site, and what pages you go to on our site. The cookie itself does not have personal information in it, so no one except us can figure out who you are from our cookie. We use cookies to save your time while using the website, remind us who you are, and track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. Cookies also allow us to collect non-personally identifiable information from you, like which pages you visited and what links you clicked on. Use of this information helps us to create a more user-friendly experience for all visitors.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies, if you prefer. This may, however, prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

  5. **Data Sharing**

We may share your information with service providers who may provide some services through us. We may share your information with them, so that, they can contact you regarding a transaction. However, we will only share such information if you engage in an activity, and then only to those involved in that activity. We may share your information with authorized third party service providers. We provide some of our services through third parties. These “Third Party Service Providers” perform functions on our behalf, like sending out and distributing our administrative and promotional emails. We may share your other information with such Service Providers to send postal or email, administer contests or sweepstakes, remove repetitive information on customer lists, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide search results and links, process credit card payments, operate the Website, troubleshoot, and provide customer service. We may also collect personal information from individuals and companies (“Affiliates”) with whom we have business relationships and may have to also share their information with Service Providers to accomplish our administrative tasks. Information collected shall not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which the information was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. Personal information shall be retained only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. If we have reason to believe that disclosing your personal identification is required by law, or is otherwise reasonable to protect someone from possible injury, we may do so.

Though we make all effort to preserve your privacy we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith and belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our website.

  6. **Log Data**

Whenever you browse our website, our servers automatically record those information sent by your browser. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer and tune the operation of our site, and to log your browser type and referring URL information. Your IP address may also be used in collecting statistical data such as number of "hits" and "page views" which is gathered for broad usage information only. None of this information can identify you personally.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.

  7. **Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials, email, SMS and other information that might be relevant to you.

  8. **Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies, which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

  9. **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

The Privacy Policy may be changed at any time upon our sole discretion and without prior notice to you. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective immediately when posted on the Website. It is your responsibility to review the Website and the Privacy Policy periodically to learn of any revisions to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Website after the effectiveness of such revisions will constitute your acknowledgment and acceptance of the terms of the revised Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided to us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
